H-Help me!
Get out of here.
Wh-What is this thing?
Didn't you hear me? Get out of here now.
Or perhaps your life doesn't matter to you?
Well, hurry.
The fun's just getting started.
Well, I guess I can't use that anymore...
Lightning?
It was terrible!
Is that woman really a devil?
There's no mistaking it.
The town fell into ruin soon
after that woman arrived.
There are people who saw
her commanding devils.
And...
And?
I saw it too...
That woman manipulating lightning
and burning people of our town to death!
I've been looking for you.
So you're the devil laying
waste to this town.
Why don't you take your true form?
That's when you're at your strongest, right?
You don't think you're a little cocky?
So you prefer to remain in that form, do you?
Well, regardless of the form
you take, I'm going to hunt you.
How long do you think you can keep
that smart-ass expression on your face?
Well, I guess my job won't be
over until I take that chick out...
Ridiculous... Who the hell'd
wear anything that expensive?
With that much money, I could drink all night
at the bar where Cindy works
and still come home with change.
Damn, that sure was a stupid bet I made.
Thinking about dressing up in drag?
Let me know if there's anything
you think would look good on me.
God... Your jokes are always so lame.
So what do you want?
If you're here to collect money
from me, I don't need that right now.
Relax. I just dropped by today
because I have something to ask you.
The truth is that, yesterday, the devil
I was supposed to bag got away from me.
Poor bastard. So I guess he'll be
hunted by you until he's dead, eh?
He's got my sympathy.
You wouldn't happen to
know anything about a she-devil
--that can command lightning, would you?
--Lightning?
Yep. Though she looked human...
Not a clue.
But there's tons of devils out there
in the world that look totally human.
Oh yeah, and she was packing heat too.
Well, devils do have fingers...
That's all you need to pull a trigger.
You got a point there.
It's just that this she-devil
fought with a gun in each hand...
Just like you.
Later.
This chick sounds interesting.
You should introduce us when you catch her.
I could teach her how to use those guns.
That won't happen... because
the next time I see her, she's dead.
You're one scary woman...
Lady!
Are you leaving already?
Sorry. Next time we'll
hang out and play together.
Sure.
Dante! So did you have a good look at this?
Listen to you... did you
forget how old you are?
There aren't any clothes for kids in there.
Hey, if you're going to buy me
clothes,  I want to get some cute stuff!
Remind me why I should
have to buy you cute clothes...
You promised you would!
You said if you lost to me at
cards, you'd buy me some clothes!
That was just yesterday. I didn't say
I'd go out and buy them for you today.
That's not fair!
You have any idea how
much those clothes cost?
Didn't you get paid yet
for tracking down that guy?
That "guy" ended up being just some runaway
lizard... You can imagine what that pays.
No, I can't.
Well, it turned out that it pays three
pizzas and two strawberry sundaes.
Pizza again?
So if you want clothes like that, you better
do something, like find a rich guy to marry.
But this is just a regular fashion magazine.
It's not like it's just the
expensive brand-names in here...
Regular kids really wear
stuff that's this expensive?
That's how it is for girls!
You don't understand
anything about girls' fashion!
For crying out loud...
Lightning...
This is the the Devil May Cry.
So it was you...
So what's the big game
you're after this time?
It isn't that big.
Actually, it's only about
the size of a human.
What? You shoot 'em with a gun
like that and they'll be minced meat!
That's fine if you're
looking to become a butcher.
Well, I doubt that I'd end
up needing to use it, but...
--Hey!
--Huh?
Is that beautiful woman
out there someone you know?
She's gone? I know I saw her here.
Wh-What the...?! What just happened?!
So that's revenge for yesterday, is it?
You don't do things half-assed.
What did you do to her?
Nothing really. We're just
having a little spat, that's all.
Huh?
Looks like I had better
change before I go to work.
Later. I'm taking this with me.
That woman always scares me.
Though the other chick must be
something, too, to be spatting with her.
You better get ready...
devil-bitch!
All these expenses!
I should bill that priest for this
stuff, but I doubt he'd cover it...
Excuse me, I'd like to try this stuff on.
Forgive me, but there's another
customer in the dressing room right now.
Would you wait just a moment, please?
Huh? What awful style.
A devil out shopping?
My, aren't we full of ourselves?
Get out of here.
I'd hate to go at it here with you
and destroy my favorite boutique.
Are you going to purchase all of this?
This is all from this year's collection.
I think you'll look great in it.
Please make sure to come and visit us again.
--Weird, I feel like I'm losing a fight...
--Also, with today's purchase at our store...
Hey, can you bring me a bunch
of those clothes from over there?
What do you think you're doing?!
You let that dangerous devil get away?!
If things continue like this, the damage
could spread to other towns as well...
She's terrible!
I didn't really think
she was all that terrible...
What are you saying?!
Do you know how many
of our brethren she's killed?
Well, I'll admit she's strong.
And I've even begun
considering using this thing...
At any rate, take care of that
devil as quickly as you can!
I know, I know. Besides, it looks
like she's here already, anyway...
We just keep running into each other today...
I may have let you get away at that boutique,
but this time I'm going to kill you for sure.
I don't care if this
church falls to the ground...
Not to mention, I'm a little pissed
off at how much these clothes cost
that I had to buy because of you!
I can't have you ignoring me.
You're in the way.
You should get out of here now.
Well he's out of the way.
Now I'll do as I like.
A two-gun toting she-devil...
It's not often I run into enemies
that I'm so averse to losing to!
Looks like your clothes
have been ruined again...
But your body seems to be faring quite well.
So, I guess you'll have
to allow me to use this!
You bitch! You shot my hair on purpose!
What's the matter? It feels like
I'm just fighting another human!
If you're going to continue like that,
you should go find some
underground club or something.
Your little show could
probably bring in some money.
Dante, that woman--
--You're late.
--Am I? What time is it?
Too bad, it doesn't look like
there's a clock around here.
I told you not to be late.
I'm here, am I not?
Just a minute...
Well it's fine since we're both okay,
but what would you have
done if one of us was killed?
Relax. Neither of you seem
like you'd go and die that easily.
--Hey!
--Huh?
What is going on here?!
What do you mean, "what's going on here"?
Are you two playing some sort of joke on me?!
You better not tell me there
were cameras rolling all along!
Umm...
And what's your deal? You can speak, huh?
So were you just playing mute?
You're quite the actress.
Would you say something here?
Don't look at me.
You're the one who said it.
That there seemed to have been
a misunderstanding,
so you'd have some fun with it...
Well yeah, but...
"Misunderstanding"?
I trust you'll explain this thing
from the beginning so I understand it?
I'm sorry for having put you on.
I'm Trish, Dante's partner.
Ex-partner. Nowadays we work independently.
That's not a very nice way to put it.
It was your idea, wasn't it?
That we'd probably work
more efficiently apart.
Are you pouting? Maybe you're
lonely being all on your own?
Don't talk to me like I'm a kid.
I totally dig being on my own.
Plus, I can eat all the pizza I want.
Didn't I tell you to go easy on the pizza?!
Don't tell me that's all
you're eating every day...
Please, don't talk to
me like you're my mom...
I said I want you to explain what's going on.
I don't give a damn about
your personal lives.
If you're feeling jealousy, you
should just let yourself express it.
That can be cute, you know.
Jealousy?
You think I'm jealous?!
He's a good-for-nothing strawberry
sundae freak who eats pizza every day
and never pays back the money he borrows!
How exactly am I supposed to fall for him?!
Oh! So I'm wrong?!
Take a wild guess!
Say something, you!
Like I said, don't look at me.
Why didn't you just
explain things to me right away?
Then we wouldn't have had to
ruin our clothes and hair, right?
I think you understand.
In this business, sometimes you can
be starving for powerful enemies.
Especially recently, when
everything we go up against is easy.
And at any rate, you seemed like
you'd give me more fun than my quarry.
Quarry?
Why don't you come on out?
You've been watching us
all along, haven't you?
I see...
I'm here at the request of another person.
Since this strange priest showed up,
this town has become a den for devils.
And he felt like he was in
danger, so he hired me...
Don't misunderstand. Putting
an end to you three will be easy.
I just thought I'd like to
avoid the hassle of doing so.
I thought he was strange, but I would
never have guessed he was a devil.
Now that you know me for
what I am, I have no choice.
It's a bit of a hassle, but you're
all going to have to die here.
What do you think of this guy?
It's unfortunate for him.
Since he's new to town, he
probably doesn't know about us.
I could almost cry of embarrassment
knowing this dork had me fooled...
Enough with your jokes!
Come back another time!
So where are you off to this time?
I've got a lot of them that I'm following.
I guess it depends on them.
If you get sick of it, you
can always come back here.
Why, that's uncharacteristically kind of you!
But for the time being, I think
I want to travel around a bit.
Take care of yourself, alright?
You too.
I'll drive you partway. Jump on.
Those clothes look good on you.
Did you go shopping again?
Yeah, I sent him the bill...
Oh, you too?
Meaning...?
I got a dress.
Nice.
Um... Are you Dante?
Huh?
I was told to bring you this bill.
No, you got the wrong guy.
No, no, no... I'm sure this is the place!
Two separate women gave me the same address.
Two women?
What?! Those two!
Would you please pay this?!
Just... Just a damn minute!
I don't have any money now!
Well, I need to be paid!
I can't give you money I
don't have. What d'ya do?
I can't just let you off with that.
What is this for in the first
place? What did they buy?!
Clothes.
Clothes? Why the hell
would clothes cost this much?!
I hope Dante won't be mad that I just
went out and bought some clothes.
Well, it should be fine. He's the
one who said he'd buy them for me!
Every now and then there's someone
who'll sneak around and spy on me.
I don't know what anyone
gets out of following around
and investigating a normal,
upright citizen such as me.
Must be a boring job... I tip my hat to 'em.
But if anyone is going to follow me around,
they'd better be ready for the
all the danger that comes with it.
'Cuz there are plenty of devils
that like to follow me around too.